wildaboutmovies.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy - Wild About Movies

Wild About Movies Entertainment’s Privacy Policy

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how Wild About Movies LLC, its subsidiary and affiliate corporations, successors, and assigns (collectively referred to as “Wild About Movies”) uses and protects the information you provide. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to this World Wide Web site and any other websites owned or operated by Wild About Movies or that may be subsequently added, variations or successors to this website (www.WildAboutMovies.com, the “Wild About Movies Sites”), any Wild About Movies computer software downloadable or otherwise available from the Wild About Movies Sites (“Wild About Movies Software”) and any Wild About Movies services purchased or otherwise made available from the Wild About Movies Sites (“Wild About Movies Services”) (collectively, the “Wild About Movies Properties”). This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to all Users (“Users”) of the Wild About Movies Properties.

A. WHAT INFORMATION Wild About Movies COLLECTS FROM YOU

Wild About Movies may collect two (2) types of information about you: Personal and Non-Personal.

1\. “Personal Information.” Personal Information refers to information that lets Wild About Movies know the specifics of who you are and which may be used to identify, contact or locate you (e.g. name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address). Wild About Movies may collect Personal Information when you use the Wild About Movies Properties including, without limitation, setting up account information, filling out surveys, corresponding with Wild About Movies, or otherwise volunteering information about yourself.

2\. “Non-Personal Information.” Non-Personal Information refers to information that, by itself, does not identify you as a specific individual (e.g. demographic information or website visitations). Wild About Movies may collect Non-Personal Information through any of the methods discussed above as well as automatically through use of industry standard technologies described further below.

B. HOW Wild About Movies COLLECTS YOUR INFORMATION

The Personal Information practices set forth apply to all of Wild About Movies’s visitors worldwide.

1\. Registration. Prior to using one or more of the Wild About Movies Properties, Wild About Movies may require certain Personal Information and Non-Personal Information to create an individual account (“Account”) or to enable features or functionality of the Wild About Movies Properties. Failure to provide all required information required by Wild About Movies may prevent access to any or all Wild About Movies Properties, and failure to maintain accurate information may result in suspension or termination of access to any or all Wild About Movies Properties.

2\. Information Collected Through Technology. While you are able to visit the Wild About Movies Sites and remain anonymous, Wild About Movies or its third party service providers may still collect Non-Personal Information about your use of the Wild About Movies Properties (e.g. your Internet browser, operating system, IP address, connection speed, and the domain name of your Internet service provider). Such information may be gathered by the following methods:

(a) Cookies. Cookies, including local shared objects, are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive which work by assigning to your computer a unique number that has no meaning outside of the Wild About Movies Sites. Cookies do not generally contain any Personal Information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually configure your browser to prevent this. Not accepting cookies may make certain features of the Wild About Movies Properties unavailable to you. Wild About Movies respects the user’s wish for anonymity and avoiding cookies.

Wild About Movies may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

(b) IP Address. You may visit many areas of the Wild About Movies Sites anonymously without the need to become a registered User. Even in such cases, Wild About Movies may collect IP addresses automatically. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you begin Services with an Internet services provider. Each time you access the Wild About Movies Sites and each time you request one of Wild About Movies’s pages, the server logs your IP address.

(c) Web Beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in web pages and e-mails. Wild About Movies may use these technical methods in/ e-mails that Wild About Movies sends to Users to determine whether they have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is Personal Information.

(d) Tracking Content Usage. If you use the Wild About Movies Services and you post audio visual materials including, without limitation, text, logos, artwork, graphics, pictures, advertisements, sound and other related intellectual property contained in such materials (collectively, “Content”) to your website or to a third party website, Wild About Movies tracks and captures Non-Personal Information associated with User accounts and the use of Content.

C. HOW Wild About Movies USES YOUR INFORMATION

1\. System Administration. Wild About Movies may use Non-Personal Information for the purposes of system administration, assisting in diagnosing problems with Wild About Movies servers, monitoring Wild About Movies’ system performance and traffic on the Wild About Movies Properties and to gather broad demographic information about Wild About Movies visitors.

2\. Personalization. Wild About Movies uses Cookies and IP Addresses to track features such as delivering Content specific to your interests and informing you of new, relevant services or certain third party offerings.

3\. Notices to Registered Users. If you have registered for an Account, Wild About Movies may use your Personal Information to send e-mails regarding your registration, including confirmation to verify the accuracy of any information you have provided, and instructions on how to post Content. Wild About Movies may also send you e-mails to verify your identity or to notify you if Wild About Movies believes your use of Wild About Movies Properties violates any applicable agreement for the use of the Wild About Movies Properties.

4\. Advertising. Wild About Movies may use Non-Personal Information to assist in optimizing the delivery of advertisements to viewers of your Content.

5\. Promotional E-mails. Wild About Movies may use your Personal Information to send you e-mails periodically listing promotions or events relating to the Wild About Movies Properties or from Wild About Movies’s marketing partners or sponsors. You have the choice to opt-out of receiving such promotional e-mails by sending an e-mail to support @Wild About Movies.com and/or following the instructions in such correspondence. Once Wild About Movies’s has processed your opt-out request, Wild About Movies will not send you promotional e-mails unless you opt back in to receiving such communications.

6\. Contact Information. If you contact Wild About Movies by telephone, e-mail or letter, Wild About Movies may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence. If you report a problem with the Wild About Movies Properties, Wild About Movies may collect this information in a file specific to you. You may contact Wild About Movies at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) About Movies.com to request the removal of this information from Wild About Movies’s database.

D. HOW TO ACCESS AND CHANGE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Upon request, Wild About Movies shall allow Users to update or correct Personal Information previously submitted, but only to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. Additionally, upon request, Wild About Movies shall delete Personal Information from the database where such information is stored; however, it may be impossible to entirely delete a User’s entry without some residual information being retained due to the manner in which data backups are maintained. Requests to delete Personal Information shall be submitted to support @Wild About Movies.com.

E. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

Wild About Movies does not sell, trade or rent Personal Information collected through the Wild About Movies Properties to any third party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Wild About Movies shall: (1) fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies; and (2) may be required to disclose Personal Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation.

F. SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

1\. Security Measures. Wild About Movies takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Personal Information. These include, but are not limited to, internal reviews of: (a) Wild About Movies’s data collection; (b) storage and processing practices; (c) electronic security measures; and (d) physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where Wild About Movies stores Personal Information. All Wild About Movies employees, contractors and agents who access Personal Information are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution or unauthorized use or disclosure of Personal Information.

2\. Third Party Links. The Wild About Movies Properties may contain links to third parties who may collect Personal Information and Non-Personal Information directly from you. Additionally, Wild About Movies may use third parties to provide components of the Wild About Movies Properties. In either case, such third parties may have separate privacy policies and data collection practices, independent of Wild About Movies. Wild About Movies: (a) has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions; (b) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites; and (c) does not make any warranties or representations about the contents, products or services offered on such websites or the security of any information you provide to them.

G. CHANGES TO Wild About Movies’S PRIVACY POLICY

Wild About Movies continually strives to implement new technologies and processes to better protect you, your privacy and your use of the Wild About Movies Properties. As a result, changes to this Privacy Policy may be made by Wild About Movies from time to time. In no event will these changes result in the degradation of any of the security measures designed to protect you from unauthorized disclosure, as such measures are described in this Privacy Policy.

I. CONTACT Wild About Movies

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact Wild About Movies by sending a letterto:

Wild About Movies LLC

Attn: Privacy

304 Newbury Street, Suite 212

Boston, MA 02115
